https://stampersanonymous.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Stampers Anonymous - Paper Crafting, Card Making, Scrapbooking
Welcome Paper Crafter!
Log In
ProductsCling Mounted StampsWood Mounted StampsStencilsEmbellishmentsInks & Ink PadsPaintStain & Spray StainMica SpraysAccentsGels, Mediums & GessoCleaners & RefreshersTexture PasteEmbossing PasteEmbossing Powder & GlazeCrayonsMarkers & PensAdhesivesStickles Glitter GlueStickles Glitter GelTotes & Accessory BagsTools & ApplicatorsTags, Paper & CardstockAlbumsSizzix DiesSizzix Embossing FoldersSizzix Machines & AccessoriesStorage SolutionsJournals & BooksCatalogsBrands & DesignersTim Holtz CollectionCling Mount Stamp SetsLayering StencilsMini Layering Stencil SetsWood Mounted StampsEtceteraDistress ProductsDistress Ink PadsMini Distress Ink PadsMini Distress Ink Pad KitsDistress ReinkersDistress Oxide Ink PadsDistress Oxide ReinkersDistress Oxide SpraysDistress Embossing InkDistress Embossing GlazeDistress Enamel PinsDistress BundlesDistress Texture PasteDistress Grit-PasteDistress Mixed Media PaletteDistress Archival Ink Mini KitsDistress Archival Ink ReinkersDistress MarkersDistress CrayonsDistress PaintDistress Spray StainDistress Collage MediumDistress Micro GlazeDistress Glitter DustDistress Dry GlitterDistress Paper & CardstockDistress RefresherDistress ToolsTim Holtz Alterations3-D Embossing Folder3-D ImpresslitsBigz DiesBigz Dies with Texture FadesBigz L DiesBigz XL DiesEmbossing FoldersFramelits DiesMovers & Shapers Magnetic DiesSidekick Side-OrdersSizzix AccessoriesSizzix Die Cutting MachinesSizzix Storage SolutionsThinlits DiesTim Holtz ComponentsIdea-ology FastenersIdea-ology FindingsIdea-ology TrimmingsIdea-ology PaperieIdea-ology StructuresIdea-ology TextilesIdea-ology VignetteIdea-ology AlbumsAccessory & Tote BagsDistress Glitter & Mica FlakesAlcohol PearlsAlcohol InksAlcohol Ink AccessoriesTim Holtz Cardstock & PaperTim Holtz ToolsTim Holtz StorageCatalogsStampers Anonymous ClassicsCling Mount StampsWood Mount StampsDina Wakley MediaCling Mount StampsStencilsMask + StencilScribble SticksJournalsMixed Media PaletteArchival Ink ReinkersGel MediumAccessory BagsToolsCatalogsDylusions by Dyan ReaveleyCling Mount Stamp SetsLarge Stencils (9" x 12")Small Stencils (5" x 8")Stencil SilhouettesAcrylic PaintPaint PensInk SpraysShimmer SprayInk PadsMixed Media PaletteArchival Ink ReinkersCollage SheetsColoring SheetsJournaling TagsAccessory BagsJournals & BooksCatalogsStudio 490 Wendy VecchiCling Mount Stamp SetsWood Mounted StampsBackground StampsStencils for ArtBlendable Dye Ink PadsBlendable Dye Ink ReinkersArchival Ink PadsMini Archival Ink Pad KitsArchival Ink ReinkersMixed Media PalettePerfect CardstockToolsWashi TapeEmbossing PasteEmbossing PowderKits for ArtMAT MinisMat Board ProjectsArt PartsClearly for ArtSTAMP-it! Stencil-it!Stamp & Stencil StorageAccessory BagsCatalogsThe Art of Brett WeldeleCling Mounted StampsStencilsCatalogsWhat's NewVideosConventionsAbout Us
Search:
Home
»
Privacy Policy
At Stampers Anonymous, the health and safety of our customers and employees is our top priority. We are carefully following the guidelines of the CDC and the Ohio Department of Health in response to the COVID-19 pandemic. We are accepting orders and shipping as quickly as product and staff shortages allow - orders can take up to 2 weeks to be shipped. Thank you for your continued loyalty—we really appreciate you!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how StampersAnonymous.com uses and protects any information that you give StampersAnonymous.com when you use this website. Stampers Anonymous is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Stampers Anonymous may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the list of cookies we collect see the List of Cookies We Collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers we think you may find interesting.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
GDPR Compliance
The GDPR is a new legal framework regarding data protection, from the European Union (EU) that takes effect on May 25, 2018. This law is designed to unify the current data protection privacy laws throughout the EU, and enhance the rights of citizens of the EU and protect their personal information. The GDPR applies to any business that offers products or services to the citizens of the EU or collects personal information from the citizens of the EU.
Retention of Data
We hold onto collected data indefinitely, unless an EU citizen requests their information be deleted from our records. This includes Personally Identifiable Information (PII) data as well as non-personally identifiable visitor data. We will retain and use information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations and resolve disputes.
Retrieval of Data
In compliance with the GDPR, citizens of the EU can: Request access to information we have collected about you, Correct any information we have about you, and Have any or all of your PII information deleted from our records. When requesting access to the information we have on you, we will provide you with a copy of the data we process about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted from our database.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at contact@stampersanonymous.com.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 3110 Payne Ave
Cleveland, OH 44114.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
IS_DEVELOPER_MODE
Session crypt key to indicate whether system is in developer mode.
SAAS_DESIGNEDITOR_VISUAL_BLOCK_MANAGEMENT_MODE
Indicates whether system is in visual block management mode.
SAAS_DESIGNEDITOR_THEME_PREVIEW_MODE
Indicates whether system is in theme preview mode.
SAAS_DESIGNEDITOR_INLINE_TRANSLATION_MODE
Indicates whether system is in inline translation mode.
MAGE_COOKIE
Indicates that cookies are initialized.
Art Gone Wild!
Newsletter Sign Up:
© 2020 Stampers Anonymous. All Rights Reserved.
